<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
           xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema"
           xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="Documentation/Schemas/Amplitude.Unity.Runtime.RuntimeModule.xsd">
    <RuntimeModule Name="MilitaryOutposts"
                   Type="Extension"
                   Version="1.1">
        <Title>Military Outposts</Title>

        <Description>Please remember to [img]https://i.imgur.com/fVVaDCS.gif[/img] if you enjoy the mod![hr][/hr][h1]Mod Description[/h1][hr][/hr]Have you ever wanted to take a system to secure a strategic foothold, to pressure another empire, or to simply expand - only to be slapped in the face with overcolonization penalties? Suffer no further. To address the oppresive design of the overcolonization system this mod introduces a new system improvement which can be unlocked in the 2nd tier of military technologies. Once built, this improvement will have the following effects:[list][*]+1 Systems occupied before triggering expansion dissaproval on Empire.[*]-75% FIDSI production on the System this improvement is built on.[*]+10 per population on System to ground battle deployment limit (DEF).[*]+25 per population on System to maximum manpower capacity.[/list][hr][/hr][h1]Mod Reasoning[/h1]Colonizing systems is something players should be able to do consistently do throughout the playthrough. Through this mod I hope to address the following issues I believe to be present in the base game:[list][*]Once the colonization limit is reached, the game forces you to build approval buildings in all systems if you want to expand further. This really stagnates expansion and slows down the pace of the game.[*]Players have little reason to colonize poorer quality systems (i.e. systems with few planets) in fear of hitting the colonization limit.[*]There is little strategy in terms of capturing systems, i.e. its rarely worth to go over the colonization limit just to capture a system at a chokepoint node.[*]The base game emphasis on turtling is too great. The objective of wars should be to capture new systems and not to wait out the war. However if you have already reached the colonization limit, going to war is discouraging as capturing new systems just puts you into approval chaos.[*]There is little reason to specialize a system for defences over FIDSI improvements.[/list][hr][/hr][h1]Future Development[/h1][list][*]Add custom art for the new technology/improvement.[*]Better mod logo.[*]Buff/nerf improvement effects depending on feedback.[*]Address other suggestions.[/list]If you have any suggestions or improvements for the mod, or if you have played with the mod and just have some feedback, please do not hesitate to leave a comment.[hr][/hr][h1]Compatibility[/h1]This is an Extension mod and thus should not have any compatibilty issues with other mods.</Description>

        <Author>Fadingwhite</Author>

        <Homepage>https://github.com/Fadingwhite/ES2_Mods</Homepage>

        <PreviewImageFile>ModIcon.png</PreviewImageFile>

        <ReleaseNotes>1.1: -Fix a bug with the improvement's increase to maximum manpower capacity and deployment limit not applying to the system. All effects visible on the tooltip now apply correctly.</ReleaseNotes>

        <Tags>Buildings, Gameplay, Improvements, Technologies</Tags>

        <Plugins>
            <DatabasePlugin DataType="ScienceConstructibleElement, Assembly-CSharp">
                <ExtraTypes>
                    <ExtraType DataType="TechnologyDefinition, Assembly-CSharp" />
                </ExtraTypes>

                <FilePath>Simulation/TechnologyDefinitions.xml</FilePath>
            </DatabasePlugin>

            <DatabasePlugin DataType="IndustryConstructibleElement, Assembly-CSharp">
                <ExtraTypes>
                    <ExtraType DataType="StarSystemImprovementDefinition, Assembly-CSharp" />
                </ExtraTypes>

                <FilePath>Simulation/SystemImprovementDefinitions.xml</FilePath>
            </DatabasePlugin>

            <DatabasePlugin DataType="Amplitude.Unity.Gui.GuiElement, Assembly-CSharp-firstpass">
                <ExtraTypes>
                    <ExtraType DataType="Amplitude.Unity.Gui.ExtendedGuiElement, Assembly-CSharp-firstpass" />

                    <ExtraType DataType="TechnologyGuiElement2, Assembly-CSharp" />
                </ExtraTypes>

                <FilePath>Gui/GuiElements.xml</FilePath>
            </DatabasePlugin>

            <DatabasePlugin DataType="Amplitude.Unity.Simulation.SimulationDescriptor, Assembly-CSharp-firstpass">
                <FilePath>Simulation/SimulationDescriptors.xml</FilePath>
            </DatabasePlugin>

            <LocalizationPlugin DefaultLanguage="english">
                <Directory>Localization</Directory>
            </LocalizationPlugin>
        </Plugins>
    </RuntimeModule>
</Datatable>